# VASANTH . D

Recent MBA Graduate Eager to Contribute to Business Success

## **My Contact**

vasanth979177@gmail.com

9344250479

No 11 A block police quaters madhavaram chennai 600110

linkedin.com/in/vasanth-d-182589230

#### **Hard Skill**

- · SQL programming
- · Git and GitHub
- · Power BI and Tableau
- excel

#### Soft Skill

- Observation
- · Decision making
- Communication
- · Multi-tasking

## **Education Background**

- June 2021 May 2023 SRM University MBA business administration
- July 2017 May 2020 Loyola college,
  BCA computer application

#### Extracurricular activities

ROTARACT CLUB - Loyola college , Community Service (outreach) - Loyola college

# **Languages Known**

English, Tamil

#### **About Me**

One year of Experience in the field. Handling customer in related to supply chain management and functionality issues. Providing technical assistance to customers who may be experiencing issues with products or services, troubleshooting problems, and guiding them through solutions. Passionate about area of knowledge towards problem solving and root cause analysis

## **Professional Experience**

April 2021 - October 2021

Leadline private ltd, chennai - logistics executive

- Kept detailed records of incoming and outgoing stock for diligent supply management.
- Logged outgoing deliveries in online systems, enabling automated updates for dents and customers

## **Internship**

 Hi tech plumbing workers Pvt. Ltd. 06/05/2022 - 18/06/2022
Exposed to the roles and responsibilities of sales, marketing and customer service departments in the organization.

• Real worship communication Pvt. Ltd 20/02/2023 - 10/04/2023 Human Resource (talent acquisition executive)

# **Project**

- Sports Management System frontend:PHP, backend:MYSQL
- An observation study on motivation as an effective tool for employee's performance at real worship communication. Tool used (SPSS)

## **Additional**

Workshop on Marketing Analytics Tools Workshop on MS Excel for Human Resource Management